bncnetwork.net 2011-11-13

# bncnetwork.net

You must periodically review this Privacy Policy as it may change from time to time.

Industry Networks is committed to protecting your privacy. This Industry Networks Privacy Statement applies to data collection and usage of Industry Networks programs, sites, and services. Please read the Industry Networks Privacy Statement below and also any supplementary information at the end of this statement for additional details about particular Industry Networks programs, sites and services that you may use.

Industry Networks offers industry specific information. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Statement. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
Industry Networks collects corporate and personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Industry Networks may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. Information collected by Industry Networks may be combined with information obtained from other services.

Industry Networks keeps track of the pages our customers visit within Industry Networks, in order to determine what Industry Networks programs, sites and services are the most popular. Industry Networks also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, and access times. Certain Industry Networks services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Industry Networks and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
Industry Networks and its operational service partners collect and use your information to operate Industry Networks and deliver the services you have requested. These services may include the display of customized content and advertising based upon the information Industry Networks has collected. Industry Networks does not use or disclose sensitive personal or corporate information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Industry Networks also uses your personal information to inform you of other Industry Networks or affiliate products or services that are available. Industry Networks may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Industry Networks does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Industry Networks may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Industry Networks may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Industry Networks or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Industry Networks, including its Industry Networks family of Web sites; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Industry Networks services or members of the public. Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in any country in which Industry Networks or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Industry Networks abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.  
**  
You may have the ability to view or edit your personal information:**  
Industry Networks is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Use of Cookies**  
Industry Networks uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize Industry Networks' pages, or register with Industry Networks' sites or services, a cookie helps Industry Networks to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, preferred email address, and so on. When you return to Industry Networks, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Industry Networks features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Industry Networks services or Web sites you visit. 

**Use of Web Beacons**  
Industry Networks Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow Industry Networks to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Industry Networks may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or Industry Networks Newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. Industry Networks Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there by third parties in order to compile aggregated statistics and to help determine the effectiveness of our joint promotional or advertising campaigns. Industry Networks prohibits web beacons from being used to access your personal information.

**Use of Third Party Ad Networks**  
The majority of the online banner advertisements you see on Industry Networks Web pages are displayed by Industry Networks.

In addition, Industry Networks allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on Industry Networks Web pages. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Industry Networks does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.

Industry Networks maintains relationships with a number of the third-party ad networks. Those ad networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting. You may find more information at the Web site of either the individual ad network or the Network Advertising Initiative.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses the DoubleClick DART cookie to serve advertisements on this site. Google's use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve advertisements to users based on information (not including name, address, email address, or telephone number) about their visits to this site and/or other sites on the Internet, in order to provide the most useful and relevant advertisements to users. For more information about this practice or to opt out of the use of the DoubleClick DART cookie, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Changes to this Statement**  
Industry Networks will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Industry Networks will use your personal information, Industry Networks will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Industry Networks encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Industry Networks is protecting your information.
